Guide to the Elizabeth Robins Papers 1803-1963 MSS 002
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Photographic Material
  - Subseries B: General Portraits
    - Cutter, Nina (Album 3, Photograph 118)
    - Cutter, Nina, 1884 (Album 3, Photograph 119)
    - Cutter, Nina (Album 3, Photograph 120)
    - Cutter, Nina and Mrs. Cutter (Album 3)
    - Dabbs, Mrs (Album 3, Photograph 121)
    - Dace, Reginia, ca. 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 122)
    - Daudet, Madame (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #370.
    - Davidge, Mary (Album 3, Photograph 123-124)
    - Deaves, Rillie (Album 3, Photograph 125-126)
    - Diemer, Johann, 1890 (Album 3, Photograph 127)
    - Dillon, Julia Carroll (Album 3, Photograph 128)
    - Dillon, Alice (Album 3, Photograph 129)
    - Dillon, Asabel (Album 3, Photograph 130)
    - Dillon, Julia (Album 3, Photograph 131)
    - Dreier, [Katherine?] (Album 3, Photograph 131A)
    - Dreier, Katherine (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #371-72.
    - Dreier, Margaret (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #373.
    - Dreier (Album 3)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 6, Folder 1.
    - Dreier, Mrs. Theodore (Album 3, Photograph 132)
    - Du Maurier, Gerald and Herbert Ross (Album 3)
      See Album 16, #395.
    - Duse, Eleonora (Album 3, Photograph 133)
    - Eaton, Dr. Frank (Album 3, Photograph 134)
    - Edward, Prince of Wales (Album 3, Photograph 135-136)
    - Eliot, Mather, 1935 (Album 3, Photograph 137)
    - Eliot, Etta Robins and Henrietta Eliot (Album 3, Photograph 138)
    - Esmond, H.V. (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #374.
    - Esmond, Mr. and Mrs. H.V. (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #376.
    - Ethel, Agnes (Album 3, Photograph 139-140)
    - Filippi, Rosina (Album 3)
    - Fleming, Mr. and Mrs. (Album 3, Photograph 140A)
    - Folsom, M. Josie, 1884 (Album 3, Photograph 141)
    - Forbes-Robertson, Ian, 1885 (Album 3, Photograph 142)
    - Forbes-Robertson and Beatrice Stella Campbell (Album 3)
    - Forrest, Edwin (Album 3, Photograph 143)
    - Fox, Della (Album 3, Photograph 144)
    - Frederick III, Crown Prince of Germany (Album 3, Photograph 145)
    - Fulton, Howard (Album 3, Photograph 146)
    - Gale, Minna K. (Album 3, Photograph 147)
    - Galvin, Edward T., 1882 (Album 3, Photograph 148)
    - Galvin, Mary Mack, 1882 (Album 3, Photograph 149)
    - Galvin, Rita and Mary (Album 3, Photograph 150)
    - Gartner, Raimond and Elizabeth (Album 3, Photograph 151)
    - Gartner, Elizabeth (Album 3, Photograph 152-153)
    - George, King of Greece (Album 3, Photograph 154)
    - Gilbert, John, ca. 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 155)
    - Gilbert, John (Album 3, Photograph 155A)
    - Gilder, Jeanette L. (Album 3, Photograph 156)
    - Gillette, William (Album 3, Photograph 157)
    - Goldthwaite (?), Dora (Album 3, Photograph 158)
    - Gosse, Edmund (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #377.
    - Gotsch, Elisabeth, 1936 (Album 3, Photograph 159)
    - Gould, Edith Kindon (Album 3, Photograph 160)
    - Gurney, Kate and Alma Stuart Stanley (Album 3, Photograph 161)
    - Guthrie, Bessie and Nellie Buckingham (Album 3)
    - Hanbury, Lily (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #378.
    - Hanley, Lawrence (Album 3, Photograph 162)
    - Hapgood, Norman (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #379.
    - Hare, Helen (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #380.
    - Hedley, Annie, 1879 (Album 3, Photograph 163)
    - Hedley, Mary, 1882 (Album 3, Photograph 164)
    - Hedley, Mary B. (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #381.
    - Hehir, M., 1918 (Album 3, Photograph 165)
    - Heinemann, William, 1893 (Album 3, Photograph 166)
    - Heinemann, William (Album 3, Photograph 167)
      See also Album 15, #382.
    - Heury (?), Fanny and Elizabeth Robins (Album 3)
      See Album 19, #1.
    - Hewar, Lollie P., 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 168)
    - Hogan, Elizabeth Bodine, 1912 (Album 3, Photograph 169)
    - Howard, Nelly (Album 3, Photograph 170)
    - Hubert, Marjorie (Album 3, Photograph 171)
    - Hughes, Henry A. (Album 3, Photograph 172-173)
    - Ibsen, Henrik, 1891 (Album 3, Photograph 174)
    - Ibsen, Henrik (Album 3, Photograph 175)
    - Ireland, George, 1862 (Album 3, Photograph 176)
    - Irving, Henry (Album 3, Photograph 177)
    - James, Henry (Album 3)
      See Album 16, #383.
    - Jecks, Clara M., 1891 (Album 3, Photograph 178-179)
    - Jewett, Sara, 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 180)
    - Jordan, Louise (Album 3, Photograph 181-182)
    - Jordan, Louise (Album 4, Photograph 183-185)
    - Journeay, B.H. (Album 4)
      See Album 19, #4.
    - Kealhofer, Isabel Crow (Album 4, Photograph 186-188)
    - Kellogg, Gertrude, 1888 (Album 4, Photograph 189)
    - Koehler, Charles, 1888 (Album 4, Photograph 190)
    - Langtry, Mrs. L. (Album 4, Photograph 191)
    - Lea, Marion (Album 4, Photograph 192)
    - Lea, Marion (Album 4, Photograph 193)
    - Lea, Marion (Album 4, Photograph 194-197)
    - Lories, Father General (Album 4, Photograph 198)
    - Mack children (Album 4, Photograph 199)
    - Mack, Etta (Album 4, Photograph 200)
    - Mack, Charles Samuel (Album 4, Photograph 201)
    - Mack, Mary (Album 4, Photograph 202)
    - Mack, Rebecca and Charlie (Album 4, Photograph 203-204)
    - Mack, Rebecca (Album 4, Photograph 205)
    - Mack, Samuel Ely (Album 4, Photograph 206)
    - Mansfield, Richard (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #384.
    - Maud, Mrs. L. (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #385.
    - Maurice, Edmund (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #386.
    - Maurice, Mr. and Mrs. Edmund (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #387.
    - Maveocordalo (Album 4, Photograph 207)
    - McCullough, John (Album 4, Photograph 208)
    - Melville, Emilie (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #388.
    - Meteyard, Jane (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #389.
    - Meteyard, Thomas Buford, 1928 (Album 4, Photograph 209)
    - Meteyard, Thomas Buford, 1888 (Album 4, Photograph 210)
    - Meteyard, Thomas (Album 4, Photograph 211)
    - Meteyard, Marion G. (Album 4, Photograph 212)
    - Mettke, Madame (Album 4, Photograph 213)
    - Millan, Evelyn (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #390.
    - Milne, Crichton, 1892 (Album 4, Photograph 214)
    - Milne, Crichton Jordon (Album 4, Photograph 215)
    - Montague, Harry J. (Album 4, Photograph 216-217)
    - Moodie, Louise, 1891 (Album 4, Photograph 218)
    - Moore, Margaret Hussey, 1852 (Album 4, Photograph 219)
    - Murey, Jameson (Album 4, Photograph 220)
    - O'Leary, Miriam (Album 4, Photograph 221)
    - O'Neill, James, 1882 (Album 4, Photograph 222)
    - Pankhurst, Emmeline (Album 4, Photograph 223)
    - Pankhurst, Emmeline (Album 4, Photograph 224)
    - Pankhurst, Emmeline (Album 4, Photograph 225-226)
    - Parks, Emily T., 1885 (Album 4, Photograph 227)
    - Parks family (Album 4, Photograph 228)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 229-232)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 233)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 234-235)
    - Parks, George Richmond and Jack Mason (Album 4, Photograph 236)
    - Parks, George Richmond and Jack Mason (Album 4, Photograph 237)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 238-240)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 241)
    - Parks, George Richmond (Album 4, Photograph 242-243)
      See also Album 16, #391.
    - Parmele, Annie M., 1886 (Album 4, Photograph 244)
    - Perugini, Mark (Album 4, Photograph 245)
    - Pitt, Harry M. (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #392.
    - Poe, Edgar Allan (Album 4)
      See Album 20, #2.
    - Pollock, Sir Frederick (Album 4, Photograph 246)
    - Pollock, Lady Georgina with daughter and granddaughter (Album 4, Photograph 247)
    - Potwin, Carrie (Album 4, Photograph 248)
    - Potwin, Julia (Album 4, Photograph 249)
    - Potwin, Katie, 1877 (Album 4, Photograph 250)
    - Potwin, Katie, 1879 (Album 4, Photograph 251-252)
    - Potwin, Katie, 1881 (Album 4, Photograph 253)
    - Putnam Female Seminary (Album 4, Photograph 254)
    - Raven, Grace ("Nita Sin") 1887 (Album 4, Photograph 255)
    - Reimers, Sophie (Album 4, Photograph 256)
    - Richmond, Mary and Herbert, 1909 (Album 4, Photograph 257)
    - Robins, Gurdon (Album 4, Photograph 258)
    - Robins, Margaret Dreier (Album 4, Photograph 259)
    - Robins, Mary Buck (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #393-94
    - Rogin, Ben G., 1888 (Album 4, Photograph 260)
    - Ross, Fred (Album 4, Photograph 261)
    - Ross, Herbert and Gerald Du Maurier (Album 4)
    - "Rossini" (Album 4, Photograph 262)
    - Ruskin, John (Album 4, Photograph 263)
    - Russell, M.L., 1884 (Album 4, Photograph 264)
    - Salvini, Tommaso, 1883 (Album 4, Photograph 265)
    - Salvini, Tommaso (Album 4, Photograph 266)
    - Schenibri (?), Eddie, 1890 (Album 4, Photograph 267)
    - Scott, A.V. (Album 4, Photograph 267A)
    - Scott, David (Album 4, Photograph 268-269)
    - Seoville, Harriet Beecher (Album 4, Photograph 270)
    - Sharswood, May (Album 4, Photograph 271-272)
    - Sharswood, May, 1896 (Album 4, Photograph 273)
    - Smith, Beaumont (Album 4, Photograph 274)
    - Smith, Cora Gabrielle (Album 4, Photograph 275)
    - Standing, Percy C., ca. 1891 (Album 4, Photograph 276)
    - Standley, Alma Stuart and Kate Gurney (Album 4, Photograph 277)
    - Starr, Laura B. (Album 4, Photograph 278)
    - Stead, Estelle (Album 4)
      See Album 16, #396.
    - Stead, William T., 1911 (Album 4, Photograph 279)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1894 (Album 4, Photograph 280)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis (Album 4, Photograph 281)
    - Strong, Mrs., 1900 (Album 4, Photograph 282)
    - Sullivan, Mrs. Margaret (Album 4, Photograph 283)
    - Tennyson, Alfred (Album 4, Photograph 284)
    - Terris, Mr. (Album 4, Photograph 285)
    - Terry, Ellen (Album 4, Photograph 286)
    - 286. Terry, Ellen dupe? (Album 4, Photograph 286)
    - Tevis, Lloyd, 1882 (Album 4, Photograph 287)
      See also Album 16, #397.
    - Tevis, Lizzie (Album 4, Photograph 288-289)
    - Thayer, W.S. (Album 4, Photograph 290)
    - Tree, Herbert Beerbohm, 1889 (Album 4, Photograph 291)
    - Tree, Herbert Beerbohm (Album 4, Photograph 292)
      See also Album 16, #398-401.
    - Trevelyan, Charles (Album 4, Photograph 293)
    - Trevelyan, Geoffrey, 1923 (Album 4, Photograph 294)
    - Trevelyan family (Album 4, Photograph 295)
      See also Album 16, #402.
    - Toole, J.L. (Album 4, Photograph 296)
    - Trowbridge, Adele, 1879 (Album 4, Photograph 297)
    - Trowbridge, Adele (Album 4, Photograph 208)
    - Trowbridge, Adele, 1879 (Album 4, Photograph 297)
    - Trowbridge, Adele (Album 4, Photograph 298)
    - Turner, Carrie (Album 4, Photograph 299-300)
    - Turner, Carrie (Album 4, Photograph 299-300)
    - Ulmar, Geraldine (Album 5, Photograph 301-302)
    - Urner, Edward C. (Album 5, Photograph 303)
    - Urner, Elizabeth (Album 5, Photograph 304-305)
    - Urner, Henry (?) (Album 5, Photograph 306-307)
    - Urner, Nathan D. (Album 5, Photograph 308)
    - Urner, Mr. (Album 5, Photograph 309)
    - Vezin, Hermann, 1899 (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #403.
    - Victoria, Queen of England (Album 5, Photograph 310-311)
    - Vincent, M.A. (Album 5, Photograph 312-313)
    - Von Borowsky, Lisa, 1925 (Album 5, Photograph 314)
    - Von Borowsky, Lisa, 1934 (Album 5, Photograph 315-317)
    - Von Sachs, Julius, 1884 (Album 5, Photograph 318)
    - Von Sachs, Julius, 1888 (Album 5, Photograph 319)
    - Von Sachs, Julius, 1896 (Album 5, Photograph 320)
      See also Album 19, #2.
    - Waite, M.R. (Album 5, Photograph 321)
    - Walpole, Hugh (Album 5, Photograph 322)
    - Ward, Genevieve (Album 5, Photograph 323)
    - Waters, 1905 (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #404.
    - Weston, Kendall (Album 5, Photograph 324)
    - Wheeler, Ellie (Album 5, Photograph 325)
    - Whitman, Sarah Helen (Album 5, Photograph 326-329)
    - Wilberforce, Octavia, 1943 (Album 5, Photograph 330)
    - Wilberforce, Octavia, 1943 (Album 5, Photograph 331)
    - Wilberforce, Octavia, 1943 (Album 5, Photograph 332)
    - Wilberforce, Octavia, 1943 (Album 5, Photograph 333-334)
    - Wilberforce, Octavia, 1943 (Album 5, Photograph 335)
    - Wilhelm I, Emperor of Germany (Album 5, Photograph 336)
    - Wilms, Guillermo, 1888 (Album 5, Photograph 337)
    - Wilson, Joe C., 1880 (Album 5, Photograph 338)
    - Wilson, Joe (Album 5, Photograph 339)
    - Wilson, Lillie (Album 5, Photograph 340-342)
    - Wilson, Paul H., 1880 (Album 5, Photograph 343)
    - Wilson, Tom (Album 5, Photograph 344)
    - Wilson, Thomas P., 1880 (Album 5, Photograph 345)
    - Wilson, Tom (Album 5, Photograph 346)
    - Unidentified (Album 5, Photograph 347-351)
    - Unidentified by E. Steichen, 1907 (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #405.
    - Unidentified mother and child (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #406.
    - Unidentified ?actress (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #407.
    - Unidentified ?actress (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #408.
    - Unidentified peasant women (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #409.
    - Unidentified (Album 5)
      See Album 16, #410-412.
  - Subseries C: Robins Family
    Subseries C contains photographs of Elizabeth Robins' immediate family. There are childhood portraits of her brothers and sister, and the earliest Elizabeth Robins photograph, taken when she was approximately three years old. The most numerous photographs in this subseries are of her brother, Raymond Robins, including several oversize prints. The subseries also includes three daguerreotypes.
    - Jane H. Robins (Album 6, Photograph 1-4)
    - Ephraim Robins (Album 6, Photograph 5)
      See Album 20, #5.
    - Charles E. Robins, 1871 (Album 6, Photograph 6-8)
    - Charles E. Robins (Album 6, Photograph 9-10)
    - Hannah M. Robins (Album 6, Photograph 11-12)
    - (?)Mrs. Hannah Robins (Album 6)
      See Album 13, #241.
    - Charles, Sarah and Eugene Robins (Album 6, Photograph 13)
    - Sarah Sullivan Robins (Album 6)
      See Album 20, #7.
    - Eugene Robins (Album 6, Photograph 14-17)
    - Eugene Robins, 1864 (Album 6, Photograph 18-19)
      See also Album 20, #6.
    - Elizabeth Robins, 1865? (Album 6, Photograph 20-22)
    - Elizabeth Robins, 1871 (Album 6, Photograph 23-28)
    - Edward Robins, 1864? (Album 6, Photograph 29-30)
    - Eunice (Una) Robins, 1871 (Album 6, Photograph 31-36)
    - Saxton Robins, 1871 (Album 6, Photograph 37-38)
    - Saxton Robins, 1873 (Album 6, Photograph 3941)
    - Saxton Robins (Album 6, Photograph 42)
    - Vernon Robins, 1873 (Album 6, Photograph 43)
    - Vernon Robins, 1873 (Album 6, Photograph 44-47)
    - Vernon Robins (Album 6, Photograph 48-49)
      See also Album 19, #9.
    - Vernon and Raymond Robins, 1881 (Album 6, Photograph 50)
    - Vernon Robins and "Uncle Carl" (Album 6, Photograph 51)
    - Raymond Robins (Album 6, Photograph 52)
    - Raymond Robins (Album 6, Photograph 53)
    - Raymond Robins, 1917 (Album 6, Photograph 54)
    - Raymond Robins, 1917 (Album 6, Photograph 55)
    - Raymond Robins, 1917 (Album 6, Photograph 56)
    - Raymond Robins (Album 6, Photograph 57)
      See also Album 17, #59-70.
    - Raymond Robins and Margaret Dreier Robins (Album 6, Photograph 58)
    - Photographic geneology (Album 6)
      See Album 17, #57-58.
  - Subseries D: Alaska
    Subseries D records Robins’ journey to the Alaskan Klondyke in 1900. It also includes photos given to her by friends in Alaska and those taken by commercial photographers. Gold mining, Eskimo life, Yukon River landscapes, and the early towns of Alaska receive extensive coverage. A small number of these photographs have been published in Robins' Raymond and I.
    - Alaska Photographs (Album 6, Photograph 1-335)
    - Alaska -- see Album 17, #336-421 (Album 6)
    - See also Oversize Material, Box 7, #422-423 (Album 6)
    - Alaska scrapbook (Album 7)
    - Alaska scrapbook (Album 8)
  - Subseries E: Backettstown
    Subseries E contains an album of photographs taken at Backsettown, including interior and exterior shots of the brick-and-timber main house and of people associated with life there. There are many photographs of Octavia Wilberforce farming Backsettown's fields or tending to its cows; of Elizabeth Robins's ward, David Scott, growing up there. Postcard shots of the village of Henfield and its environs are also contained in it.
    - Backsettown photographs (Album 9, Photograph 1-233)
  - Subseries F: Chinsegut
    Subseries F is made up of two albums of photographs taken at Chinsegut, the Hernando County, Florida estate where Elizabeth Robins' brother, Raymond, lived. This subseries includes many candid photographs of Margaret Dreier Robins and her sister, Mary Dreier, both of whom were active in the women's movement in the United States. The reconstruction of the main house is well documented, as are the crops, flora and fauna of Chinsegut. This subseries contains a fine collection of photographs of the black servants who worked for the Robinses, providing a chronicle of their domestic and work experiences in rural Florida during the first quarter of this century.
    - Chinsegut photographs (Album 10, Photograph 1-271)
    - Chinsegut photographs (Album 11, Photograph 272-459)
  - Subseries G: Colorado and Other Places
    Places visited by Elizabeth Robins and unidentified landscape photographs are contained in Subseries G. There are a few stereographs from Summit, Colorado, which include shots of gold mining camps.
    - Colorado: Little Annie Cabin (Album 12, Photograph 1-3)
    - Colorado: Little Annie Gold Mine (Album 12, Photograph 4-6)
    - Colorado (Album 12, Photograph 7-13)
    - Chicago, ca. 1903 (Album 12, Photograph 14-21)
    - Derwentwater, England (Album 12, Photograph 22)
    - Gallipoli (Album 12, Photograph 23-25)
    - Valour House, Southwest Harbor, Maine (Album 12, Photograph 26-27)
    - Zanesville, Ohio (Album 12, Photograph 28-29)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 7, Folders 3 and 4.
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 30-43)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 44)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 45)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 46)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 47)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 48)
    - Miscellaneous (Album 12, Photograph 49-82)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 7, Folder 5.
  - Subseries H: Negatives
    Subseries H contains all of the negatives found in Series IX; they are numbered consecutively but divided by subject categories.
    - Subseries B: Mrs. Emmeline Pankhurst (Album 13, Photograph 1-4)
    - Subseries D: Alaska (Album 13, Photograph 5-27)
    - Subseries E: Backsettown (Album 13, Photograph 28-127)
    - Subseries F: Chinsegut (Album 13, Photograph 128-240)
    - Glass negative -- (?) Mrs. Hannah Robins (Album 13, Photograph 241)
    - Glass negative -- Longfellow's "Evangeline" (Album 13, Photograph 242)
  - Over 5"x7"
    - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins (Album 14, Photograph 129-163)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 5, #164-175.
    - Subseries B: General Portraits (Album 15, Photograph 352-382)
    - Subseries B: General Portraits (Album 16, Photograph 383-412)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 6, #413-421.
    - Subseries C: Robins Family (Album 17, Photograph 52-70)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 6, #71-72.
    - Subseries D: Alaska (Album 17, Photograph 336-421)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 7, #422-423.
    - Subseries E: Backsettown (Album 18, Photograph 234-246)
    - Subseries F: Chinsegut (Album 18, Photograph 460-473)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins and ca. 1885 Fanny [Heury?], tintype (Album 19, Photograph 1)
    - Subseries B: Albert Cordes, Miss Cordes and Julius von Sachs, tintype (Album 19, Photograph 2)
    - Subseries B: Bessie Guthrie and Nellie Buckingham, tintype (Album 19, Photograph 3)
    - Subseries B: B.H. Journeay, tintype (Album 19, Photograph 4)
    - Subseries B: unidentified (Album 19, Photograph 5-8)
    - Subseries C: Vernon Robins and Mary Buck Robins scrapbook (Album 19, Photograph 9)
    - 14th Century carved ball from Peabody Museum, Salem, Massachusetts (Album 19, Photograph 10)
    - Subseries B: Edward Crow, Jr., daguerreotype (Album 20, Photograph 1)
    - Subseries B: Poe, Edgar Allen, daguerreotype (Album 20, Photograph 2)
    - Subseries B: unidentified, daguerreotypes (Album 20, Photograph 3-4)
    - Subseries C: Ephraim Robins, daguerreotype (Album 20, Photograph 5)
    - Subseries C: Eugene Robins, ?daguerreotype (Album 20, Photograph 6)
    - Subseries C: Sarah Sullivan Robins, daguerreotype (Album 20, Photograph 7)
- Series X: Legal and Financial Records
  - Subseries A: Legal Records
    The legal records in Subseries A include numerous drafts of Elizabeth Robins’ will, her marriage license, passports, literary contracts and the records related to Backsettown and her property in Florida.
    - Elizabeth Robins' Wills 1894-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Elisabeth Robins and George R. Parks 12 January 1885 Marriage License (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Inventories n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 8, Folder 2.
    - Literary Contracts 1898-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Backsettown Tenancy Agreements (Box 1, Folder 5)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 8, Folder 3.
    - Title deeds to Florida Property, correspondence (Quit Claim) 1905, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Passports and correspondence re: passports and residency 1916-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Financial Records
    Subseries B provides a record of Robins' financial history from 1894-1951 through bankbooks, securities records, royalty statements and income tax reports.
    - Bank books and account books (20 volumes) 1894-1929 (Box 2)
    - Account book, National Provincial Bank 1939-1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Weekly House Book, Albion 1927 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Royalty Statements 1895-1909 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Royalty Statements 1910-1913 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Royalty Statements 1919-1930 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      See also Box 7, Folder 33.
    - Royalty Statements 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Royalty Statements 1934-1940 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Securities Records 1918-1924 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Securities Records 1925 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Securities Records 1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Securities Records 1930 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Securities Records 1931 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Securities Records 1932 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Securities Records 1933 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Securities Records 1934 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Securities Records 1935 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Securities Records 1938-1950 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Financial Records--Annuity Purchase (Box 6, Folder 18)
      See also Series Two, Box 27, Folder 204.
    - Financial Records--Backsettown 1919-1935, 1946, 1919 -1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Financial Records--Chinsegut see Box 7, Folder 34.
    - Financial Records--Palace Gate (Box 6)
      See Oversize Material, Box 4, Folder 9.
    - Financial Records--Clement, Parker and Co. 1902-1909 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Financial Records--Gates, McCully and Buckwell 1935,1936 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Financial Records--Field, Roscoe and Co. 1949, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Financial Records--miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Financial Records--miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 24)
      See also Box 7, Folder 35.
    - Insurance Fees (correspondence) 1923, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Insurance Records-- see Oversize Material, Box 8, Folder 5.
    - Tithe Records 1929-1936 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Finances and notes concerning family burial plot 1887, 1893, 1912, 1913, n.d., 1887 -1913 (Box 6, Folder 26A)
  - Legal Size Material
    - Income Tax Records 1905-1922 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Income Tax Records 1923-1927 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Income Tax Records 1928-1932 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Income Tax Records 1935-1937 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Tax Records--Florida 1931, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Real Estate Records 1903 (Box 7, Folder 32)